Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is one of my favorite flavors,
peanut butter cup. Let me show you how
to make it. We are starting off with a
peanut butter base. This is such an
underrated base on my page. It includes
peanut butter powder as well as some
real peanut butter. So, you get the
creaminess from the peanut butter and
then all of the flavor from the peanut
butter powder. It's a great combination
of not being too high calorie, but also
packing tons of peanut butter flavor. It
also comes out super thick from the
peanut butter and given that we added a
lot of powder, I find that the more dry
ingredients you add, say powder,
sweetener, whatever, it actually comes
out thicker. So, this one was super
thick. And you could honestly eat this
just as a plain peanut butter base. But,
we're not going to leave the peanut
butter cups out in a peanut butter cup
ice cream. So, I topped mine with a few
Reese's mini peanut butter cups, and it
was delicious.